I was able to keep my engineering GPA
over 3.5, go to 15 hackathons, and also
grow to 50K on social media. This is
Gia. She's a college student who won 21
hackathons with a 70% win rate. I signed
up for the next one and actually didn't
tell my parents, uh, secretly rented a
car, drove to Ohio, and then won first
place. Not to mention that she started a
company while in college with a pretty
crazy story. I said I wanted to start a
company. So at 9:00 p.m. I started like
shipping out the MVP and at 9:00 a.m. I
posted it everywhere on Instagram. The
app crashed after like it got too much
traffic. Our apartment got robbed. We
got our laptop stolen. Um it's okay. So
literally the next hour we got right
back on to talking to clients. We landed
seven YC companies working with us and
50 other companies. I appreciated her
transparency and think you will too.
There are so many like CS content
creators getting cancelled left and
right for like their opinions on this
topic. Um, my opinion is that
the number one thing that I wanted to
talk to you about was hackathons. You
attended so many hackathons. It's crazy.
And you have an insane win rate. I don't
know. I saw I keep seeing like 70% being
thrown around there. So, okay, you
clearly have figured it out. You know
how to win hackathons. You got some
special tips here. How did you get into
the hackathons? What made you want to go
so deep into hackathons as a college
student? I got into hackathons actually
from a non-technical background. I was a
finance major. Oh, really? I had taken
one Python class, like try harded it,
sort of attended every single lecture,
got a four point, and then I was like, I
can try attending this hackathon this
weekend. The issue was that I didn't
know any of like the modern libraries
like React or Next, but I was like, oh,
there's builders at this hackathon, so I
can probably just have them like build
my idea. But I ended up building the
entire time for the full 24 hours and we
ended up like losing that first
hackathon. You said you were fine. So
did you have any experience in high
school like APCS or anything like that?
I had APCs but I was pretty like
disinterested. Okay. So you you knew
something but you didn't expect this to
be something that you got really deep
into. So after you did that first
hackathon, what made you want to do
another 20 after then? It kind of just
naturally flowed. Even though we like
lost the first hackathon, I wasn't that
disappointed because like that was the
first time where I felt so much
enthusiasm for building um and I was
able to like unleash my creativity. So I
signed up for the next one and actually
didn't tell my parents uh secretly
rented a car, drove to Ohio and then won
first place for hardware for the Ohio
hackathon. Um it was called Hacks. So
this was during this was in college,
right? This was in college. This is in
my freshman year of college in the
spring semester. Oh my god. Okay. So,
you really went out of your way. And you
did a hardware hackathon, too. Yeah. And
I did a hardware hackathon. Um I
basically had this like insane schedule
where I would take my economics courses
in in the daytime. So, just cram them
and get them out of the way. And
virtually the entire day I'd be in the
lab like experimenting with hardware,
software. And from like 9:00 p.m. to
5:00 a.m., like most days of the week, I
would just be like learning new APIs,
new tools, new libraries, um, and like
new microcontrollers. Yeah, it was it
was kind of crazy. What was the thing
that you built that won the hackathon?
Uh the thing that I built that won the
hackathon. Um basically I just put a
bunch of different modules together with
a Raspberry Pi Raspberry Pi Pico and it
was able to measure the distance between
the Raspberry Pi and uh whatever object
was in front of it. Sort of like an
extension of like a walking cane or like
invisible well not walking cane but like
yeah cane for people with like visual
disabilities. So instead of like the
cane being 10 feet, it would be like 20
feet and wherever you pointed like your
arm, you' be able to like measure the
distance. You rented a car, you kind of
just sent it. How'd you build the team?
What happened when you got there? I had
found a friend from just like reaching
out on Discord servers and so we drove
there together. Uh but I just like full
sent the hackathon solo. Oh, okay. So
you didn't you didn't have a team. Out
of all the hackathons that you do
participate in, do you feel like the
team's a big part of it or have you been
soloing all of them? A team is a big
part of it. I think when going for like
massive prizes or like going for grand
prizes, for sure a team is an advantage
rather than a disadvantage. Especially
when you can like divide tasks and
people can specialize then like when
everyone's working at the same thing
like all that manpower is extremely
helpful. What what makes a good team?
Finding teammates not based on the
credential but based on like their
skills. a lot of times like people would
ape in on like the PhD research students
um because of their credentials or
because of their internships or titles
or whatever but I would take like the
opposite route and I would look at
people's projects on GitHub see how
active their commits were and see like
what kind of experience they had with
the our particular like use case and
that was actually a better method
because these teammates would be more
passionate about the project we were
building um put in more effort and sort
of be more scrappy and have like less of
a limiting mindset and more of like a
growth mindset. That makes sense. You're
basically hiring for the exact skill set
that you need to build something. When
you come into these hackathons, do you
already come in with ideas? Yeah, I
already come in with ideas. There's so
much like
hackathons are are not like typical like
competitive programming competitions.
There's so many aspects to a hackathon
like the social aspect, the time frame
aspect, how there's like only 24 to 48
hours, the fact that there's very
different themed prizes, niche prizes
that you can research into tool into and
how the tools that you're like given are
varied. So you have to be very scrappy.
But in that way you can like sort of max
out the aspects before building or for
example like even though you don't like
type any code you can put together a
Google doc research the different
sponsor tools sort of understand how
they integrate with your different ideas
visualize how you would be developing
the project and if it's feasible within
24 hours I would often go for like a
very solid simple straightforward
finished product rather than going for
something absurd or complex. I mean in
times like I would aim high in like very
like grand prizes prizes where I do like
something extremely complex like for the
Princeton hackathon we did a lacing
algorithm for seeing if people mess with
artist NFTs. Lacing algorithm? Well,
what do you mean by lacing algorithm?
Like an algorithm that can like trace
back if someone has messed with
someone's art in an NFT and it tracks it
back to the original artist. I see.
Okay. Okay. So, there's at some point in
the tree of edits, it fans off of Okay,
I see. And you you built some UI on top
of it to like show that this was like a
descendant of some prior NFT or
something like that. Yep. Yep. I see. I
see. And that won the the grand prize
for at Princeton. Yeah. That won the
Verbar prize. I see. I see. Okay. What
So, you mentioned like the you know, in
order to win there's a social component.
Um, are you talking about the judges or
you're talking about the teams or what
is that? Both the judges and the teams.
Like for example, being able to read
people for the team and see if they
would like contribute positively or
negatively to the energy of the team
because like beyond skills, motivation
in the hackathon for the whole 24 hours
is pretty integral. Like when someone
gives up or thinks that the hackathon
isn't as possible, like there are only
like Yeah, there's only three other
people to keep the energy of the team
up. And like being like one a one person
try hard is also like motivating to the
team because they can see how serious
like one person is. But um still like
the best results have come when every
single member of the team is absolutely
full sending the hack though. Makes
sense. And you talked about the judges
are also a big part of it. Yeah you I
imagine you really have to sell your
ideas or present. That's got to be a big
part in addition to building. Do you
have any tips for people who attend the
hackathons? what works when it comes to
selling. A big misconception is that
people think that the most theoretical
ideas will win because another big
misconception about hackathons is that
they think that the most like um
theoretically correct people win it. But
that's actually not the case. Most of
these judges are actually non-technical.
So a big thing that I do is I look into
the judge's eyes and see if they're
actually following. And I also keep the
pitch very concise. I simply state the
idea, what it does, and then focus the
most on the demo and the judges
interacting with the demo. So the judges
can see for themselves that the product
actually works without cracking versus
like I've seen other approaches or
mistakes where people and also mistakes
I've made too is where people explain
about the whole tech stack and think the
judges will be impressed rather than
having them interact with a with a
project directly where they talk about
oh I use MongoDB, I use Nex.js JS and
fast API and then they keep rambling
about all the technical details, but all
the judges want to see is is this
project hype and would they imagine
themselves using it or someone they know
using it. I see. So, and when you said
theoretical, you're talking about like
technical complexity. Like a lot of
people think that it's actually a
technically complex solution that's
going to win, but it's actually the
thing that solves a real problem or is
interesting and they could really see
the the value in the project. Is that
right? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I also think
that aiming high for technical
complexity is also helpful because
pursuing a more ambitious idea but
having thought through all the steps
like in the Google doc I said makes a
very technical project seem very simple
to a judge because it's implemented with
flawless execution. So in your
experience what's more important is it
the idea for the project or is it the
execution on the project? I would say
both. So my aims would be fully connect
front end and back end to make sure it's
working and make sure the idea is very
unique. Does the back end need to be
work? I remember when I was um at UCLA
doing hackathons, we had one we trying
to get the back end of the front end to
work and we were all not great builders.
We were just good tests, taking tests
and stuff. We didn't know how to
actually build software and then so we
got the front end working but the back
end was absolutely not working at all.
And so we just made the backend like a
file or something and had the front end
just reading from that file. Uh and I
mean it it worked like if you looked at
it on you know on my local uh but
there's there's no back end. So I guess
my question is like how much does the
implementation details matter or is it
just if you show something that looks
good they're not going to add ask any
questions about what it's actually doing
and how it's doing it. I think to a
degree it can work but like if you're
aiming for the win then it's probably
better to have an actually working
project because then you can explore
more once you get it connected for
technical development a big
misconception is that when you divide
your team you can divide them into front
end and back end and at the end you can
integrate them all together and so the
front end people keep on making the
front end more beautiful they add like
more buttons they're like oh I have this
idea we're going to actually have an
entire quiz for people to take and then
the back end people are like oh let's
keep on building the back end we're
going to think about the different
tables to add. We're going to see how if
it can like load faster and then at the
end it never gets fully integrated. So
the actual approach would be within the
first few hours connect the front end
and back end together even if like in
the most simple way at the like the
earliest stage possible and then iterate
on that. So see if the websockets are
streaming see how the connection works
set up the port whatever. Right. Right.
That makes sense. Out of all of the
projects that you've done, I mean over
or over over 20 hackathons, do you have
any favorite projects? I think my
favorite project is
this VR that we built completely from
cardboard and glass and we use like an
Arduino to project in glass prism in a
hologram through like cardboard glasses
a transcription using AI transcription.
We use whisper AI and like projected the
live transcription in a hologram through
the VR. It was pretty awesome. What was
using the light? It was like a projector
or something. Uh yeah, it was like an
OLED from like an OLED screen that you
can like integrate with an Arduino. Oh,
interesting. And we connected it all
through Bluetooth and then Yeah. So if
you were a student in class and your
professor was talking but you couldn't
pay attention, like all the notes would
pop up in a hologram on the top right of
your glasses and then also get
summarized in the web app. Oh, that that
is that's crazy. I don't know. And you
did that in 24 hours? We did that in 9
hours and we're able to sleep the
hackathon. That's why it was insane. The
entire team was cracked. No, I believe
kids students there are just community
college kids. We literally drove
there absolutely full sent the project.
Yeah, that's crazy. How'd you put
together that team? There's this guy
just like at a community college nearby
who was just building rockets in his
backyard and I was like, "Yo, want to go
to hackathon?" And he was like, "Bet it
up.
And then like at my AD club, there were
just these guys that were always working
in the entrepreneurship center. Um, and
like they just had like the grind set.
They just worked all the time. And so I
was like, "Y'all want to do a
hackathon?" And so then that was us
four. And we are all still in contact
today. Wow. Okay. That's that's crazy.
This random community college kid
building rockets in his backyard. That's
that's a really interesting hire for
your team. I'm curious. Would you
recommend hackathons? And if so, what
are the benefits? Because I remember
when I was I was a long time ago, but it
wasn't really the top priority. There's
a lot of other things to focus on. Why
should someone do hackathons? I think in
this day and age with like the
competition in the market, it's really
good to have personal projects that make
you stand out. But I also think that
like the marginal benefit of hackathons
decreases and it'd be much more valuable
to just make a product that people want
to use like longterm or just get a bunch
of users. I think you learn more from
that. But yeah, at hackathons they have
recruiters there. They fasttrack you to
applications like for example Bloomberg,
Rooflow. They're looking for builders.
Hackathons also help you develop agency.
being able to just like think on your
feet, do something new, not be afraid to
do something new, and not be afraid to
do it in in an environment you don't
know anything about. So yeah, being
adaptable. I'd say I think like three
hackathons is good. Three to five, but
anything after that like probably not
the best for like body or Yeah. You
could be doing something else.
For sure. For sure. So you said
basically it's a it's a forcing function
to building a project. But you think the
thing that actually helps people learn
and distinguish themselves is actually
not the hackathon. It's the project and
building something that matters that
people are using that is what helps
people stand out for recruiters. Is that
right? Yeah. Well, stand out for
recruiters and also just learn more than
you would at hackathons. I see. I see.
That's why I hackathons. Yeah. Yeah. I
mean hackathons it's literally in the
name. It's just the most insane hack.
It's it's not there's probably not a
long not a lot of long-term learnings
from something that's thrown together so
quickly. You mentioned agency. That's
really interesting because that actually
stood out to me. You're talking about
you random you just got got in a car.
You just sent it to some random
hackathon without telling your parents
and you went and you it it worked out
and you won. The thing that stands out
to me is not you winning, but it's the
not the audacity, but the initiative to
kind of just go not take permission and
just go and send it. Um, I'm curious, do
you feel like it's a muscle or do you
feel like your agency has gotten
stronger over time? Always had like a
little bit. Yeah, there's a point to
where I got so bored of school like I
just needed some sort of mental
stimulation that wasn't like
regurgitating information from like a
textbook. I don't know. I think maybe
it's like the deviation from where I
came from. Like for example like no name
state school starting a company is like
pretty much unheard of. There are like
two or three people that like were very
serious about startups from that school.
I'd like to think that yeah hackathons
did increase my agency. You talk about
school. I mean when I was going to
school I felt like it was taking a good
amount of time. I can't imagine
balancing all this stuff. I mean you're
also doing social media startup
hackathon. So that's something I'm
curious about is like how do you
prioritize? How do you manage your time?
Okay. Well, there was this one semester
back when I actually did care about like
everything and I was like I had to do
all of it because I just want to make
everyone happy. Like I had to do grades
to make my parents happy. I had to do
hackathons to make myself happy. I had
to do content to put myself out there
and get a job. And that was that was a
lot of pressure. But I was able to keep
my 3.5 engineering GPA, keep my
engineering GPA over 3.5, go to 15
hackathons and also grow to 50K on
social media. Oh my god, that was like I
think that was like the semester before
last semester. And yeah, last semester I
just kind of full sent it on doing
things I wanted instead of school. But
yeah, that one semester where I was
focused on like all three. The way I
managed my time is that I would like do
time blocking. So if I had like a task
of homework to do, I would set a
specific time during the day to execute
on it and also location. And then for
hackathons, I would make sure like all
my homework was done before Friday at
5:00 p.m. so I could focus on the win
for the hackathon because I see some
people doing a homework at hackathons.
And I would know I think full focus like
in the environment you're in is good.
And then for content, I sort of just
like started to understand short form
content and how you can put like a
minimal amount of effort into one piece
of short form content but get like a lot
of leverage in the future. So like I
would just make like 3 second to 5
second reels that would just get a ton
of views or like casual reels wherever I
was in the day. Like yeah, there's 24
hours in the day and enough time for a
one minute reel. So yeah, I would just
like wherever I was I would just like
you know film that Walmart reel. I think
a lot of people overthink content and
think that it's hard to balance, but
short form content is pretty okay. I
see. Okay. So, your answer to the
balance is
just efficiency and Yeah. Yeah. Time
blocking. Yeah. Time blocking and then
also prioritizing the most impactful
stuff cuz it sounds like you're you
weren't the type of creator for instance
in the content where you were really
sweating long videos or posting
non-stop. you really thought about this
is like the highest ROI video. Yeah.
Yeah. And it's short, I'm just going to
send it and then move on, do the next
thing. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Oh, and then
also attending office hours like for all
the hardest classes like even if I
wasn't doing if I didn't have specific
questions, I just like sort of sit in
there and like just acquire information
from everyone else's questions and as
well the professor just like sort of
like mentioning offhand, oh, this is
going to be like something important on
the exam. just like being there in
person or like being at hackathons in
person. Environment placement is pretty
big. So I I also took that with me like
when I went to Silicon Valley to be
there for in the startup land when
building a startup. Right. Right. Right.
Right. No, that makes sense. It's it's
more efficient. You get more out of it.
There's so many I guess second order
effects of choosing what environment you
put yourself in. You mentioned that you
attended a non-target school. How do you
think about for people who are not
attending a major bigname school? What
do you need to do in order to succeed?
Become a decision maker in the area. So
whether it's like leadership in clubs
like being decision maker there or like
being a decision maker for a like a big
project that a lot of people use whether
it's like not a company but like a big
side project or or something you do with
your friends or being a decision maker
for like content or having like a
personal brand. Yeah. Maybe in short
this is all just to say work on your
agency so you can stand out. I see.
Okay. So, you're basically saying if
your school's not an outlier, you should
be an outlier in the things that you do.
And and that's that's what drew you to
content. Is that right? I mostly did it
for fun, too. But that was probably one
of the reasons. Yeah. What do you
think's the most important takeaway from
college? Or do you feel like college was
this thing where you just checked in,
checked out, but it really didn't
matter? There are so many like CS
content creators getting cancelled left
and right for like their opinions on
this topic. My opinion is that it works
for some people. It gives them structure
and discipline. I think it's useful to
have a structure especially when there
hasn't been that much agency built up.
If you don't know what to learn, they
just like provide it for you. It's also
like a great way to meet people and
buildings together. So like people the
same age. But like the another like I
guess my other view on it is for like
for me personally, it definitely like
dulled down my creativity and my passion
for learning. Not everyone needs it, but
it's good to have for a start and also
very admirable or like respectable to
finish and continue going on that path
to big tech or whatever. I think the
structure can be good when you just
don't know exactly like what you want to
do and also if you know what you want to
do as well because it's just like a
direct path into something that could be
really amazing for you and be like
really structured for your life. I I
guess I'm curious because in your case,
your agency is just like off the charts.
If you didn't go to college, do you
think it would have made much
difference? I don't know. In high
school, I was already doing like
non-typical stuff. I guess I was putting
music out on Spotify. I had like a music
career. My parents, I don't know how
they felt about that, but I got 150k
streams and I was like I was like going
to just keep on going to I was just
going to keep on being a music artist.
Like people in my high school were like,
"Wait, you post music on Spotify. We've
not heard about that." But um okay,
college did help me find hackathons. I
think I think everything that I have
every experience I've done in my life up
to now has still contributed to the
person I am now. That makes sense. Is
there something that you wish you knew
before you got into college? Something I
wish I knew before I got into college
was how much network really did matter?
I think like knowing the right
opportunities, having the right people
advise the college application because
despite good test scores or GPA or
whatever in high school like that would
still get beat out by people with like
research internships or good like
referral letters also how much like
network can propel a person in like any
stage of their career. this I don't know
this might be like I don't know if this
is the common take or I don't know how
popular this take is but yeah I think
network is pretty powerful even if a
person is on the same like skill scale
or the people they know or the people
they intentionally go out to get to know
can really like change the trajectory of
where they go for sure you asked how
popular is this opinion yeah I don't
think it's a hot take I think everything
in this world is uh or not well
everything is strong word But most
things are decided by people. And so
imagine you said you wanted a Disney
internship. Imagine if you knew someone
on the team and they were looking for an
intern or you want to start a company
and maybe you want to get into YC. You
know, someone can it can help or also
with privileged information too. I think
that's a large part why I do this this
podcast. Imagine someone knew you, they
could ask you all these things, get a a
leg ahead when it comes to hackathons
and all those things. or we can just
give it to everyone for free. So yeah,
you know this this is giving that
privilege information more people. Yeah,
I love that mission. I'm curious about
the content stuff. How'd you get into
creating content? Well, I had been
making music content for a while cuz
like cue the the Spotify career whatever
but a friend from high school told me to
vlog a hackathon video and I was like
that seems fun and I didn't do it for a
while until like I think by the time it
was like my 16th hackathon win I just
gave it a try and it blew up. People
love interesting videos. They also like
to see big cash money won by student.
So yeah, that that really helped, I
guess. What was the price like from
there? The prize was like, I think
$3,000 first place grand prize. Wow.
Yeah, that's pretty good. Especially for
college. For college? Yeah, for sure.
Oh, yeah. Okay, that makes sense. What's
your definition of personal brand?
Something that is helpful or relevant
for college kids? I think it's good to
have a personal brand for students no
matter like what environment you're
from. I think what it does is just it
gives you leverage instead of sharing it
to five people. Any subsequent action
just gets built up by the time you like
make a project and it's really cool.
Instead of getting to five recruiters,
it could just get to like 500 all at one
point and increases like the chances of
good opportunity reaching you. Yeah.
Increases your luck and the
opportunities. I think a lot of people
get scared or they could agree and be
like, "Yeah, it's a good idea. I should
post that project I built on LinkedIn or
whatever, but I think a lot of people
are scared to put themselves out there."
How did you get over that when you were
first getting into it? I think like I
consulted like some close friends about
it first and even if they weren't
creator friends just like talking to
other people about ideas and having them
support and like having that be
something grounding and being like oh
there are going to be three people who
support me no matter what even if like
the hundred people or something maybe
think I'm cringe or don't like it and
like it is those three people that
matter the most. I mean, there probably
are some other creators that phrase it
better, but that's like what ground
guided me. Being scared, but doing it
despite that because you have a support
network. Yeah, support network. Not
every single person is going to be
posting all the time. If you think about
just your average college student that
wants to be slightly more visible or
stick out to recruiters, what's a
concrete thing that you'd recommend they
do? Get out of local host. um post your
project on the cloud and even if you
don't post it on LinkedIn or Instagram
like you'll have it on GitHub, you can
send it to recruiters or put yourself
out there. Yeah. And it's easier to link
it to GitHub as well. Right. Right.
Right. Okay. So, you're take you're
saying take the work, make it public.
Don't just have it be some clos Okay.
You're taking a gap semester in SF. I
think that's pretty unusual for college
kids who working on a startup. What's
the story behind how that happened?
Well, the startup started on a Thursday
night when I was bored and I said I
wanted to start a company. So, at 9:00
p.m. I started like shipping out the MVP
and at 9:00 a.m. I posted it everywhere
on Instagram. The app crashed after like
it got too much traffic. I I just like I
was like never mind. I started the app
because of all the comments on Instagram
about hackathons and I was trying to
make an an app that like helped people
learn how to get into hackathons. But
yeah, then a few months later, I met my
co-founder Aiden, who helped me get the
app back up, and we went to a Lake Tahoe
trip to go skiing with our hackathon
friends. But we ended up staying in SF,
raising angel investment at a Luma
event, like a hot pot, and then raising
VC investment at another Luma event. So,
at that point, we were like, yo, let's
go forward with this. And this VC
investment over hot pot. Was it a VC
event or you just happened to meet
someone at this hot pot thing that was
like, "Hey, here's an angel check." Oh,
yeah. The angel investment was at the
hot pot and I just happened to meet
someone who was like so intrigued by our
story that he put in an angel check cuz
like basically we were crashing all over
in motel shipping out the product. We
had a lot of traction at the time. I
think 5,000 users and a lot of like when
we were already making revenue from like
B2B. So sort of told him about how I did
all these hackathons and I'm now making
hackathon app. I think he liked the
product market fit or the founder market
fit. Yeah. He was like, "Yo, can I put a
check in?" And some other angel investor
overheard in the table and then they
both put checks in. And then I posted a
video about getting the checks and it
blew up to 500K on Instagram and there's
another angel's put checks in. Wow.
Okay. You just pro and two of the things
you said were your network matters.
Okay. Boom. That's the beginning of
this, right? And then the other thing
was the leverage of content. Boom.
That's where the other 13 checks came
from. So, um Okay.
Wow. All right. Do you think you'll go
back to to college? Likely won't be
going back to MSU, but I could transfer
to like a school in California and
you're that's another thing you said is
like placing yourself in the right spot.
So, it sounds like California is a very
big difference from where where you
were. Yeah. You know, when you start a
company, you probably get a lot of
advice. Is there any particularly good
advice that you've got? I think good
advice is like to move fast and keep
shipping. And another piece of good
advice is don't burn out, which are like
two like oppositives. Yeah, two
oppositives. I think it makes sense like
just keep on like consistently shipping
fast, but also like when you need a
break, probably take it because like it
really will weigh on like other parts of
your life like relationships or your own
mental health and things like that. And
so I think when I first received that
advice, I was like, eh, like let's just
keep on pushing. and that it did come
invite me back later. But yeah, if
that's something I could tell people
about startups is that there is probably
like a healthier way to go about
startups like even if it's like a few
hours of break or doing something Yeah.
that's not company or workrelated
probably probably helpful. So did you
burn out and how did you know that you
had burnt out? I didn't burn out but I
definitely felt like pressed like I
think I wasn't able I wasn't able to
afford to burn out. We were definitely
in a scrappy environment. Like we were
in Soma and our apartment got robbed. Oh
man. So we literally had to just like
even if I even if I was going to burn
out, I was literally pressed. Like we
like emailed like hundred other clients
that that very day. Like we just
couldn't like Yeah, that was that was a
tough time for sure. Or we got our
laptop stolen. We got all my jewelry
stolen and my co-founders watch. But
it's okay. The next literally the next
hour we got right back on to talking to
clients. We landed seven YC companies
working with us and 50 other companies.
So we reach we reached five we reached
five figures MR this month and congrats.
Yeah, that sounds stressful. Even if I
didn't burn out, it's still like weighed
hard on other aspects of my life like
mental health and relationships. Yeah.
Let's say there's a kid who's going to
college. They're thinking about quitting
and starting their own company. Is that
something you'd recommend? What do you
need to see where you feel that's a good
idea? I think I would not recommend
dropping out immediately. I would
recommend setting win conditions
depending on what kind of person you are
or how much you know yourself. My win
conditions were like, do I have the
background in the network to be able to
raise investment? Do I have the skills
that I would need to be able to land
clients and like survive in SF on like
my own money and my co-founders money?
and like yeah technical skills like
knowing I was with the right people to
like build out this product and also
like be able to market out market it out
to or have distribution systems for
people. So like yeah my win conditions
were distribution system technical
ability to execute on the project yeah
confidence in like my own network for
both clients investments. So clearly
you're coming into this very different
from someone who just fresh wants to
just start a startup. you had all these
preconditions that were going to really
increase your chances of success knowing
what you know now. Would you advise
people go into computer science after,
you know, going through recruiting and
seeing what it's like? Ooh, it's another
one of those questions where it's like
it really depends on the person. But I
would recommend always trying to build
like always trying it out. Um trying out
building something that people want or
and people will use cuz there's only
like an upside to it. It's either a you
figure out oh I built something that I
want like people want to use and I'm
just gonna keep building something
people want to use or you build
something people want to use people use
it and then the recruiters love it. So
for sure like if there's one one thing
to just like straightforward tell people
is try and build something that people
want to use. Okay cool. And then yeah
the last thing is is this one thing that
you wish you could tell yourself before
you got into college? What would that
one thing be? be more open, say yes to
more things that bring you connection or
like teachings. I think I was a lot more
like I'd only hang out with a few
specific people. Whenever people like it
wouldn't invite me out, I would probably
be like, "Oh, no. If you're a CS major
that's like not touching grass or like a
high schooler that's not touching grass,
probably go and touch grass." That's
what I'd tell myself back then is That's
interesting you say that cuz I feel like
you're
pretty willing to say yes to things. So
you've grown now and this is okay. This
is Okay. Okay. You touch grass now? M
That's debatable, but a little bit more.
Yeah. A little bit more. Okay, cool.
Awesome. Okay. Well, yeah, that's I
think that's everything that I had. If
you want, now's the time. If you want to
plug something or maybe talk about the
startup, you can feel free to talk and
maybe people will go check it out. Yeah,
sure. Yeah, the startup I co-founded
with Aiden Goolan is sprint.dev. If
you're a student or any like any age
developer, this is an easier way to
enter hackathons. And we're looking for
the best builders. By best, I don't mean
like the most technically developed or
like the best ranked. I mean best as in
you're willing to have creativity,
execute on it, and you're willing to
work with others, collaborate, and ship
out things that people will love. You
can go to sprint.dev, dev and there are
a lot of free tools out there both for
hackathons and also like company prizes.
When you sign up for a hackathon, one of
our hackathons will immediately provide
you with like API credits and support on
our discord so you can be less afraid to
attend hackathons and be more happy to
make friends. Sprint.dev Dev like sprint
as in like fast running and dev as in
dev.